[
  {
    "product_id": 1,
    "licence_name": "STARWARS",
    "category_name‚Äù": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "BABY YODA BLUEBALL",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "STW001001",
    "img_front": "../multimedia/star-wars/baby-yoda-1.webp",
    "img_back": "../multimedia/star-wars/baby-yoda-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 2,
    "licence_name": "STARWARS",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "BOBA FETT FIGHTER",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "STW001002",
    "img_front": "../multimedia/star-wars/bobbafeth-1.webp",
    "img_back": "../multimedia/star-wars/bobbafeth-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 3,
    "licence_name": "STARWARS",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "LUKE AND GROGU",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "STW001003",
    "img_front": "../multimedia/star-wars/luke-1.webp",
    "img_back": "../multimedia/star-wars/luke-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 4,
    "licence_name": "STARWARS",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "STORMTROPPER",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "STW001004",
    "img_front": "../multimedia/star-wars/trooper-1.webp",
    "img_back": "../multimedia/star-wars/trooper-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 5,
    "licence_name": "POKEMON",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "CHARMANDER",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "PKM001001",
    "img_front": "../multimedia/pokemon/charmander-1.webp",
    "img_back": "../multimedia/pokemon/charmander-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 6,
    "licence_name": "POKEMON",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "DRAGONITE",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "PKM001002",
    "img_front": "../multimedia/pokemon/dragonite-1.webp",
    "img_back": "../multimedia/pokemon/dragonite-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 7,
    "licence_name": "POKEMON",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "PIDGEOTTO",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "PKM001003",
    "img_front": "../multimedia/pokemon/pidgeotto-1.webp",
    "img_back": "../multimedia/pokemon/pidgeotto-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 8,
    "licence_name": "POKEMON",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": " PIKACHU",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "PKM001004",
    "img_front": "../multimedia/pokemon/pikachu-1.webp",
    "img_back": "../multimedia/pokemon/pikachu-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 9,
    "licence_name": "POKEMON",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "VULPIX",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "PKM001005",
    "img_front": "../multimedia/pokemon/vulpix-1.webp",
    "img_back": "../multimedia/pokemon/vulpix-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 10,
    "licence_name": "HARRY POTTER",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "HARRY",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable harry potter",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "HPT001001",
    "img_front": "../multimedia/harry-potter/harry-1.webp",
    "img_back": "../multimedia/harry-potter/harry-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 11,
    "licence_name": "HARRY POTTER",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "HERMIONE",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable harry potter",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "HPT001002",
    "img_front": "../multimedia/harry-potter/hermione-1.webp",
    "img_back": "../multimedia/harry-potter/hermione-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 12,
    "licence_name": "HARRY POTTER",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "LUNA",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable harry potter",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "HPT001003",
    "img_front": "../multimedia/harry-potter/luna-1.webp",
    "img_back": "../multimedia/harry-potter/luna-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 13,
    "licence_name": "HARRY POTTER",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "SNAPE PATRONUS",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable harry potter",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "HPT001004",
    "img_front": "../multimedia/harry-potter/snape-patronus-1.webp",
    "img_back": "../multimedia/harry-potter/snape-patronus-box.webp"
  },
]
